<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://LemurianAdventureGuild.github.io/wiki/news</id>
    <title>Lemurian Adventure Guild Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://LemurianAdventureGuild.github.io/wiki/news"/>
    <subtitle>Lemurian Adventure Guild Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://LemurianAdventureGuild.github.io/wiki/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LEMURIAN GUILD ACCUSED OF GROSS MISCONDUCT, UNDER INQUIRY BY THE CROWN]]></title>
        <id>https://LemurianAdventureGuild.github.io/wiki/news/2023/08/22/expose</id>
        <link href="https://LemurianAdventureGuild.github.io/wiki/news/2023/08/22/expose"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An official Kingdom Inquiry is underway as several accounts of gross misconduct have been leveled at the Lemurian Guild. “We are taking these accusations seriously and will fully comply with the investigative process,” stated Lady Cecilia, Commander of the Lemurian Guild.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>An official Kingdom Inquiry is underway as several accounts of gross misconduct have been leveled at the Lemurian Guild. “We are taking these accusations seriously and will fully comply with the investigative process,” stated Lady Cecilia, Commander of the Lemurian Guild. </p><p>The Court hears complaints about the Lemurian Guild with some frequency, but rarely do these escalate to the point of a formal inquiry. Three incidents in quick succession appear to have been substantiated enough to begin the process.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="animal-abusers">ANIMAL ABUSERS?<a href="#animal-abusers" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to ANIMAL ABUSERS?" title="Direct link to ANIMAL ABUSERS?">​</a></h2><p>A passionate druid described a bloody scene in the forests outside the Capital. This time of year, food is scarce as the area goes through a natural transition towards winter. The druid brought a particularly cognizant squirrel who stated for the Court that members of the Lemurian Guild came, gathered these hungry animals together, then threw a bag of food into the center and watched as the animals fought one another to claim it. These Guild members then captured the squirrel and tortured him for information on the location of an item the squirrel found abandoned in the woods.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="toturers">TOTURERS?<a href="#toturers" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to TOTURERS?" title="Direct link to TOTURERS?">​</a></h2><p>Shortly thereafter, the Court received a letter from Numergard where a small-time inmate described in detail how he was captured by the Lemurian Guild and placed into a cell for several weeks. While in the Guild’s cells, he overheard another inmate being tortured for information. “It was awful. I could hear the screaming as he said over and over how he could not give them the information they wanted,” read the letter.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="thieves">THIEVES?<a href="#thieves" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to THIEVES?" title="Direct link to THIEVES?">​</a></h2><p>Two additional accounts of assault and robbery in locations and times where and when Guild missions were authorized. Lady Cecilia stated that the Guild was using an internal process to look into these events to see if Guild members were involved, but at this point, the King authorized the Court to proceed with an inquiry into Guild records.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="guilds-statement">GUILD'S STATEMENT<a href="#guilds-statement" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to GUILD'S STATEMENT" title="Direct link to GUILD'S STATEMENT">​</a></h2><p>Lady Cecilia faced scrutiny from the Court during proceedings for her failure to keep the Guild under control as its commander. She responded, “We allow our members a high amount of autonomy so they may react to the unpredictable situations and varied dangers that threaten our fair kingdom. I know what it is like to go into awful situations and have to make hard choices in the heat of battle with lives on the line,” she said, referring to her time as an active combatant in the Guild which earned her the moniker ‘the Silver Valkyrie’. “That being said, we as the Lemurian Guild must hold ourselves to a higher standard commensurate with the power we wield.”</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="guild-gone-rogue">GUILD GONE ROGUE?<a href="#guild-gone-rogue" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to GUILD GONE ROGUE?" title="Direct link to GUILD GONE ROGUE?">​</a></h2><p>Just last year, the Guild also faced scrutiny for performing missions without following proper reporting guidelines. In an expose published by this author, it was revealed that a number of missions took place without documentation in hopes of keeping those missions secret. This prompted an inquiry and establishment of new regulations on when and how missions are documented and reported to the Crown and Court.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Writ Scribbler</name>
        </author>
        <category label="expose" term="expose"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Weekly Scribbles]]></title>
        <id>https://LemurianAdventureGuild.github.io/wiki/news/2023/08/22/the-weekly-scribbles</id>
        <link href="https://LemurianAdventureGuild.github.io/wiki/news/2023/08/22/the-weekly-scribbles"/>
        <updated>2023-08-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Real world week 8/22 edition]]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>[Real world week 8/22 edition]</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="people-of-nortia-disappear-without-a-trace">People of Nortia Disappear Without a Trace<a href="#people-of-nortia-disappear-without-a-trace" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to People of Nortia Disappear Without a Trace" title="Direct link to People of Nortia Disappear Without a Trace">​</a></h2><p>Nortia, a small province at the northwestern edge of the Kingdom, continues to experience hardship. First unusual weather patterns have forced the area into perpetual overcast for months, which is starting to impact crop yields. Trade caravans and travelers have gone missing. And now this week, there are reports of an entire town of people suddenly going missing. Mister White and his son took a shipment of goods to the next town down the road, stayed the night, and when they returned, they found the entire village had vanished. There were no signs of struggle nor any damage to buildings observed. “It’s like they all just decided to walk away,” said a confused Mister White.</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="alvis-announces-international-tour">Alvis Announces International Tour<a href="#alvis-announces-international-tour" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Alvis Announces International Tour" title="Direct link to Alvis Announces International Tour">​</a></h2><p>Beloved entertainer Alvis Parsley has announced another world tour. The King of Bards now heads to the East where he will play at several venues across all 7 major countries. Most of the time will be spent in the Carmel Kingdom and Hershey Empire. “I had to cut my last tour short for personal reasons,” Alvis said in an interview. “Now that things are a little more settled, it’s time to get back to doing what I do best: bringing hope and joy to the people of the world.”</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="art-heist-of-the-century">Art Heist of the Century<a href="#art-heist-of-the-century" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Art Heist of the Century" title="Direct link to Art Heist of the Century">​</a></h2><p>In Xanthium, the Phantom Thieves have struck again. This time they targeted the Rikplatz Museum which earlier this week debuted seven new Donatello paintings. When museum staff arrived this morning, they found all seven paintings missing and the word “STOLEN” was painted on the now empty wall space. The customary calling card was also found, which denounced Donatello as a plagiarist who claimed his apprentices’ artwork as his own. Donatello asserts that the accusation is false and that the thieves are trying to discredit his good name. Xanthium investigators are baffled, and even the Lemurian Guild seems to have made little headway in apprehending the Phantom Thieves.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Writ Scribbler</name>
        </author>
        <category label="The Weekly Scribbles" term="The Weekly Scribbles"/>
    </entry>
</feed>